https://inspectusa.com/privacy.php

View all Reviews
4-in-1 Anemometer (LM-8000A) Air Speed, Temp, Humidity & Light: At first I thought I was shorted th...  Sonin Rapitest Moisture Meter 10-28% (50211) Coiled Cable: Good meter. Reliable and easy to re...  Wireless Water Alarm Kit (WA318) with Remote Sensor: You should advertise this to everyo...  Safety Siren Radon Gas Monitor & Alarm (HS71512): Arrived quick. It works....  Refrigerator Alarm (HAM02) Alerts When Door is Open 30 Seconds: I am glad I found this in your clos...  Radon Test Short Term Liquid Scintillation (rn-LS) Lab Fee Included: ...
Blog
About Us
Contact Us
New Products
Radon Results
My Account
Log In
My Account My Orders My Address Book My Password
0 item(s)
0 item(s), $0.00
JavaScript seems to be disabled in your browser.You must have JavaScript enabled in your browser to utilize the functionality of this website.Click here for instructions on enabling javascript in your browser.
Meters, Test Kits, Inspection Supplies & Tools!
Advanced Search
Categories
Air Quality - IAQAnemometers-Air FlowCarbon Monoxide (CO)EMF / Microwave MetersFire and Smoke Safety Fire and Smoke SafetyAerosols & CartridgesPoles & AccessoriesSmoke DetectorsGas and Leak DetectorsHeat Detector TestingHeat Index MonitorsHygiene / Food SafetyHygrometers / HumidityInspection Supplies Inspection SuppliesBorescopes BorescopesScope AccessoriesLights / Flashlights Lights / FlashlightsStreamLight AccessoriesMagnifiers / BinocularsInstrument CasesLight, LUX, UV MetersManometers / PressureMeasuring InstrumentsMeter Accessories Meter AccessoriesParts and SuppliesPower AdaptersSoftware & CablesMoisture MetersPower & Circuit TestersRadon Mitigation & Fans Radon Mitigation & FansCouplings/ Install KitsMitigation AccessoriesWater VOC SystemsRadon Testing & Kits Radon Testing & KitsNJ Radon Test KitsRefractometers - BRIXSafety and Security Safety and SecurityMetal DetectorsSmoke Trace EmittersSoil & Grain MetersSound Level MetersSpecialty Instruments Specialty InstrumentsCombustion AnalyzersThermometersThermometers InfraredTimers and ClocksTools and HardwareWater & Flood AlarmsWater Testing Water TestingWater Meter ProbesProbes & LeadsPromotional ItemsOutlet / Overstock
HomeCatalogPrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Inspect USA ® cares about protecting your personal information, we appreciate your trust and want to ensure
you that your information will be used carefully and sensibly. By visiting InspectUSA.com, you are accepting the practices described in this
Privacy Policy.Opt-out ChoiceYou can opt-out as follows:
forward the email, account or correspondence in question to us: Contact us
Why Do We Gather Customer Information? The limited information we obtain helps us personalize and continually improve your
shopping experience. We only store information you enter on our web site when you search, buy, bid, post, participate in a contest or
questionnaire, update your account or communicate with customer service. We use the information you provide to respond to your requests, customize future
shopping visits, improve our store and communicate with you. To provide better product
recommendations, special offers we think will interest you or other personalized services, we might receive information about you from other sources and add it to your
account. Updated delivery and address information, from our shippers or other sources, is used to validate our records to improve future
deliveries or correspondence.
Cookies - We also use cookies, which are alphanumeric identifiers transferred to your computer through your web browser,
to enable our store to recognize and remember you. Cookies provide features such as automatic login and permanent shopping carts that can hold items you put in your shopping cart between visits.
Cookies also allow you to take full advantage of some of InspectUSA.com's most interesting features and we recommend that you configure your browser to accept them.
You have no obligation to provide any information or receive correspondence even though it might be needed to make a purchase.
Receiving eMail is voluntary and you can adjust the settings on the newsletter menu in your account to control correspondence.
Inspect USA ® Does Not Sell Customer Information - Your information is an important part of our business and
we do not sell it. We share customer information only within our organization. Sometimes we send offers to selected groups of customers on behalf of
other businesses, but we do not provide your name and address. If you do not want to receive such offers please adjust your
account newsletter preference to "no".
We may employ other companies and individuals to fulfill orders, deliver packages, send postal mail and eMail, remove repetitive
information from customer lists, analyze data, provide marketing assistance, process credit card payments and provide customer service. These people or companies have access to
personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. Other than as stated above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third
parties and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.
As Inspect USA ® grows, we might sell or buy other stores or assets. In such transactions,
customer information is one of the transferred business assets. We may also release account and other personal information when we believe it is
appropriate to comply with law enforcement; for fraud protection and credit risk reduction; to enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or to protect the
rights, property, or safety of Inspect USA ®, our users or others.
Inspect USA® Protects Your Information - We work very hard to protect the security of your information during transmission and we do NOT store credit card numbers. (Which is why we ask you to repeat your credit card number if there is ever a change to your transaction.)
We also use PayPal as one of our credit card processors, which prevents our store from seeing your credit card number. PayPal protects your privacy and information by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL)
software, which encrypts information you input. You can also protect against unauthorized access to your account by always signing off when finished using a shared computer.
Revisions - If you choose to visit InspectUSA.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice,
limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of North Carolina. If you have any concern about privacy on this web site,
please Send us a thorough description and we will try to resolve it. This Privacy Notice may change and any use of the information we gather will always be subject to the Privacy Notice in effect at the time of use so please check our web site frequently to see the most recent Privacy Notice.
Continue
Categories
Air Quality - IAQAnemometers-Air FlowCarbon Monoxide (CO)EMF / Microwave MetersFire and Smoke SafetyGas and Leak DetectorsHeat Detector TestingHeat Index MonitorsHygiene / Food SafetyHygrometers / HumidityInspection SuppliesInstrument CasesLight, LUX, UV MetersManometers / PressureMeasuring InstrumentsMeter AccessoriesMoisture MetersPower & Circuit TestersRadon Mitigation & FansRadon Testing & KitsRefractometers - BRIXSafety and SecuritySmoke Trace EmittersSoil & Grain MetersSound Level MetersSpecialty InstrumentsThermometersThermometers InfraredTimers and ClocksTools and HardwareWater & Flood AlarmsWater TestingProbes & LeadsPromotional ItemsOutlet / Overstock
Manufacturers
Please Select3MAccustar LabsAcerBoxAir Products-ControlsAiRaiderBicBjornaxBlack & DeckerBruntonBushnellBW TechnologiesCEM MetersChampion SprayOnCirrus OutdoorsConfirm BiosciencesCorentiumDakota WatchesDAPDelmhorstDuracellDwyerEnergizerEtconEternaBondExcel CarbonlessExtechFamily SafetyFFE UKFirecomFlir SystemsGarrett Metal DetectorsGeneral ToolsGersonGlo-ToobGuardian SurvivalhChekHeads UpHealthwayHome SafeguardHoneywellHygienaInficonInfinityInovaInspectUSAInspectUSA RadonITSJDC InstrumentsKane MayKiddeLacrosse TechnologyLascar ElectronicsLeathermanLeicaLignomatLutronMagniiMannix InstrumentsMaxell BatteriesMetris InstrumentsMustang KnivesNew BalanceNikon Sport OpticsNSPOntario KnifeOregon ScientificP3 InternationalPrincetonTecProtimeterProVisionPurTestQuantum GroupRadonAwayRadStarReginRhinoRialcoSaeVuSantronicsSDI FireSEI InternationalSkyLinkSolo TestersSoninSonySpruceStaplesStayWarmStorm CaseStreamlightSun NuclearSuuntoTenmarsTestiFireThe Weather ChannelTranscendTruTestUEIUnited CutleryUniversal SecurityVellemanVO ScopeXeno EnergyZTS inc
Information
Cable Length Calculator
Carbon Monoxide Gas
Radon Gas Facts
Smoke Calculator
Shopping Cart
0 items
$0.00
TruTest 801 Detector Sensitivity Tester (TT801) Head & Processor
$6,595.96 now $5,495.00
Quick Find
Use keywords to find the product you are looking for.Advanced Search
The Crazy Deal
Bestsellers
Custom Imprinted Carbon Monoxide Detector (cP2) CO Badge
Carbon Monoxide Safety Badge 2"x2" (cP1) CO Gas Detector Portable
Clean Trace Protein Plus Surface Test Swab (MT1) 10 Minute Result
What's New?
Copyright InspectUSA.com®.
All rights reserved. 1995-2020 •
No part of this website may be reproduced without our express consent.
Distributors of TestKits, Inspection Tools, HVAC Smoke & Food Safety Equipment.
